All four teams have assembled.
四支队伍全部集结完毕。
Today, you will operate as teams.
今天，你们将作为团队运作。
Team combat.
团队作战。
Blue Team's puzzle is correct.
蓝队的谜题是正确的。
Please collect the fourth key.
请收集第四把钥匙。
Got it.
知道了。
This one should definitely work.
这绝对应该有效。
Because this is the final lock.
因为这是最后的锁。
Kick one to me.
给我踢一脚。
Five
五
Kick one
踢一脚
It was entirely you two who led us to victory.
完全是你们两个带领我们取得了胜利。
No.
不。
During the final shuttlecock kicking round,
在最后一轮踢毽子时，
Lu Wanfei very bravely stepped forward
陆婉菲很勇敢的上前
and helped us complete the challenge.
并帮助我们完成了挑战。
This secured first place for our team.
这为我们队确保了第一名。
I think both of their performances
我觉得他们俩的表演
were absolutely outstanding.
绝对出色。
Since today wasn't a competition,
由于今天不是比赛，
our competitive spirit emerged.
我们的竞争精神出现了。
We really wanted to win,
我们真的很想赢，
and that winning moment was so joyful.
那个胜利的时刻是如此的快乐。
It felt like this game brought the three of us
感觉这个游戏让我们三个人
closer together.
靠得更近了。
Our little group became more united.
我们的小团体变得更加团结。
I think having one person kick more,
我认为一个人踢得更多，
five times.
五次。
That's amazing!
太棒了！
We're not in a hurry anymore.
我们不再着急了。
Since we've already done that, it doesn't matter.
既然我们已经这么做了，那就没关系了。
Let's just enjoy the fun.
让我们尽情享受乐趣吧。
Right?
正确的？
Is it now?
现在是吗？
This whole section is correct.
整个部分都是正确的。
This side.
这一边。
But this side is wrong.
但这一边是错误的。
Just these four are incorrect.
只是这四个是不正确的。
No problem, we'll switch one.
没问题，我们就换一个。
Let's change these four first.
我们先改变这四个。
Done.
完毕。
Wait, they don't match.
等等，他们不匹配。
Flip it around.
把它翻转过来。
This should work.
这应该有效。
There.
那里。
What about that side?
那边呢？
This is good.
这很好。
Okay.
好的。
Ready?
准备好？
Yes, his is correct.
是的，他的说法是正确的。
Xu Duocheng's team solved the puzzle correctly.
徐多成团队正确解开了这个谜题。
Go.
去。
It's open.
它是开放的。
Move.
移动。
Thanks.
谢谢。
What now?
现在怎么办？
Kick the shuttlecock.
踢毽子。
I thought it was over.
我以为一切都结束了。
Your turn, three.
轮到你了，三。
Right.
正确的。
Right? Then that's it.
正确的？然后就这样了。
One, two, three.
一二三。
It's okay.
没关系。
No problem, let's try again.
没问题，我们再试一次。
You start.
你开始吧。
You show it to him, right?
你给他看，对吗？
Right?
正确的？
Wrong.
错误的。
Although we didn't win
虽然我们没有赢
everyone tried their best
每个人都尽力了
especially He Jinyi
especially He Jinyi
She fought particularly hard for our team
她为我们队特别努力
I think she's truly amazing
我认为她真的很棒
They don't need to struggle anymore
他们不需要再挣扎
Yes, this is correct
是的，这是正确的
It looks right from here
从这里看起来就对了
See, this side is correct
看，这一面是正确的
Because the pieces fit together
因为各个部分组合在一起
This move
这一举动
Game over
游戏结束
All members please return to the center
请所有会员返回中心
So our result is last place
所以我们的结果是最后一名
I've been losing for three straight days
我已经连续输了三天了
But I think
但我认为
winning or losing might not be what matters most
输赢或许并不是最重要的
Because I believe in that process
因为我相信这个过程
if we form some connections
如果我们建立一些联系
if we coordinate well
如果我们协调得好
or if we put in the effort
或者如果我们付出努力
that's how we create
这就是我们创造的方式
emotional bonds
情感纽带
I believe this is what matters most
我相信这是最重要的
Our team looks so good together.
我们的团队在一起看起来很好。
What a satisfying day.
多么满足的一天啊。
My two teammates carried me hard today.
今天我的两个队友给了我很大的帮助。
So satisfying.
太令人满意了。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
Let's go back and finish assembling it.
我们回去完成组装吧。
No, that's wrong.
不，那是错误的。
Brainless and Grumpy.
无脑且脾气暴躁。
I messed up the assembly, really.
我真的把组装弄乱了。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
No, it's fine.
不，没关系。
Although we lost the match,
虽然我们输掉了比赛，
Guo Xu stayed by my side
郭旭一直在我身边
comforting me.
安慰我。
I think he has a sunny personality.
我觉得他性格阳光。
It's quite enjoyable being with him.
和他在一起真的很愉快。
Xiao Enya actually performed very well.
萧恩雅其实表现得非常好。
Though we lost today, we can fight again tomorrow.
虽然今天输了，但明天我们还能再战。
If I win the game tomorrow,
如果明天比赛我赢了
I'll choose Xiao Enya first
我先选小恩雅
to go on a date with me.
和我去约会。
Now announcing the task results:
现将任务结果公布：
First place:
首位：
Blue Team.
蓝队。
Second place:
亚军：
Yellow Team.
黄队。
Third place:
第三名：
Orange Team.
橙队。
Fourth place:
第四名：
Purple Team.
紫队。
The first place winners:
第一名获得者：
Fu Jie, Weng Fanxi, Lu Wanfei.
Fu Jie, Weng Fanxi, Lu Wanfei.
You will receive island date invitation privileges.
您将获得海岛约会邀请特权。
You may proceed to the preference scale
您可以继续选择偏好等级
to make your selection.
做出您的选择。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Go.
去。
About the dating privilege, how should we decide?
关于约会特权，我们该如何决定？
The three of us...
我们三个人...
You two go choose first.
你们两个先去选择吧。
I don't know who to pick.
我不知道该选谁。
I really want some ice water.
我真的想要一些冰水。
Go get it from the ice machine.
去制冰机取吧。
I'll go get it.
我去拿。
You're injured.
你受伤了。
Just a little.
只是一点点。
I have iodine, do you want some?
我有碘，你要吗？
How do you have everything?
你怎么拥有一切？
I just do, I have it.
我就是有，我有。
Where are you? Let me rinse it for you.
你在哪里？让我给你冲洗一下。
Here.
这里。
So when you go out, do you usually...
那么，当你外出时，你通常会...
I always bring these essentials with me.
我总是随身携带这些必需品。
Here.
这里。
It's quite painful.
这是相当痛苦的。
I also want to share many of my thoughts with you.
我也想和大家分享我的很多想法。
Did you touch something?
你碰过什么东西吗？
I think I did my best today.
我想我今天已经尽力了。
I definitely gave it 200%.
我绝对给了它200%。
If you like them, why not pursue them?
如果你喜欢他们，为什么不追求他们呢？
If you don’t act today,
如果你今天不行动的话
someone else will take them tomorrow.
明天会有人带他们去。
Here's the ice.
这是冰。
Ready to use.
准备使用。
Thank you.
谢谢。
What happened to your hand?
你的手怎么了？
It's cut.
被砍了
Got pricked by a branch while climbing.
爬山时被树枝扎伤。
Should we ice it?
我们应该冰敷它吗？
You should ice it first.
你应该先冰敷它。
Shouldn’t we cover the wound first?
不是应该先包扎伤口吗？
Because it might...
因为它可能...
This water is dirty.
这水很脏。
Right.
正确的。
The water is dirty.
水很脏。
I don’t think icing is needed—it’s not swollen.
我认为不需要冰敷——它没有肿胀。
That makes sense, right?
这有道理，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
This is...
这是...
This one?
这个？
Yes.
是的。
Alright, you can try it.
好的，你可以尝试一下。
Should we stick it here too?
我们也应该把它贴在这里吗？
Let's stick it below instead.
让我们把它贴在下面。
It hurts so much.
太疼了。
Really?
真的吗？
It hurts—really bad.
很痛——真的很痛。
Is it really that painful?
真的有那么痛苦吗？
It really is.
确实如此。
I almost cried out just now.
我刚才差点哭出来。
Seriously.
严重地。
Fine, I won’t wash my hands today.
好吧，我今天不洗手。
No hand-washing today.
今天没有洗手。
I'm going to get the supplies.
我去拿物资。
Big watermelon
大西瓜
What good stuff did you bring?
你带来了什么好东西？
You know what I brought
你知道我带来了什么
Why are you holding a knife?
你为什么拿着刀？
Watermelon
西瓜
I love eating it
我很喜欢吃它
And it's chilled
而且是冰镇的
Isn't it refreshing?
是不是很清爽呢？
I really want to eat it
我真的很想吃
Let's eat together
我们一起吃饭吧
Sis, we're "real siblings"
姐姐，我们是“真正的兄妹”
Can I have one?
我可以拥有一个吗？
Of course, help yourself
当然要帮自己
Guaranteed ripe
保证成熟
Here, let me show you
在这里，让我给你展示一下
Such a huge watermelon
这么大的西瓜
So happy
太高兴了
Let's share with them
让我们与他们分享
Have a piece
来一块
Take a piece
取一块
After spending these days together
经过这些天的相处
I think Hu Wei has a great personality
我觉得胡伟很有个性
Very kind-hearted
非常善良
My fondness for her isn't just about looks
我对她的喜爱不仅仅是外表
I admire her inner qualities more
我更欣赏她的内在品质
Have a piece, bro
来一块吧兄弟
In my eyes, there's only her
我的眼里只有她
The chilled one is so refreshing
冰镇过的真清爽
Here
这里
Here, eat this
来，吃这个
It's delicious
很好吃
Sit down
坐下
Really tasty
真的很好吃
You have great taste
你很有品味
"Melon King"
“瓜王”
So happy—we won
太高兴了——我们赢了
This makes it worthwhile
这使得它值得
Seeing you enjoy this bite makes it worth it
看到你享受这一口就值得了
What matters most is having the upper hand
最重要的是占据上风
You really like being in control
你真的很喜欢掌控一切
I'm thrilled
我很激动
But now I’m worried—who to choose?
但现在我很担心——该选谁呢？
Right, who should we pick?
对了，我们该选谁呢？
What do we do?
我们做什么？
This power to choose...
这个选择的权力...
feels like a burden to me
对我来说感觉像是一种负担
Really?
真的吗？
Truly
确实
I don't know how to choose
我不知道如何选择
It's so hard
太难了
Hurry up and make a decision
赶快做出决定
I think we can all move on now
我想我们现在都可以继续前进
Islanders who have obtained dating invitation rights
已获得约会邀请权的岛民
Fu Jie
Fu Jie
Weng Fanxi
Weng Fanxi
Lu Wanfei
Lu Wanfei
You may proceed to the Scale of Preference in turn
您可以依次进入偏好等级
Other islanders please be prepared
其他岛民请做好准备
and await invitation notifications
并等待邀请通知
Can people from the same group go on a date together?
同一群人可以一起去约会吗？
I choose both of you.
我选择你们两个。
Thank you.
谢谢。
You sit in the middle.
你坐在中间。
The middle.
中间。
Let me wipe your sweat
让我帮你擦汗
What's going on, my bro
发生什么事了，我的兄弟
Three, two, one
三、二、一
Yes
是的
The question I want to ask is
我想问的问题是
Has Daniel ever chosen me before?
丹尼尔以前选择过我吗？
No
不
Okay
好的
Have you made your choice?
你做出选择了吗？
I think I'll just give up.
我想我会放弃。
Why?
为什么？
Don't give up. Why would you give up?
不要放弃。你为什么要放弃？
I'm just going to quit.
我要退出了。
I don't know who to date.
我不知道该和谁约会。
Zhang Xin left with Tao Zhiquan.
Zhang Xin left with Tao Zhiquan.
There are no other guys who are serious about me.
没有其他人对我认真。
Now everyone's situation is...
现在大家的情况是...
gradually becoming clearer.
逐渐变得清晰起来。
And I'm too passive. If...
而且我也太被动了。如果...
no one takes the initiative to approach me,
没有人主动接近我，
it's hard for me to reach out to others.
我很难接触到其他人。
I think you should treat it as...
我认为你应该把它当作...
If tomorrow...
如果明天...
someone might leave,
有人可能会离开，
and you still want to talk to them,
而你仍然想和他们交谈
I think you should take this opportunity
我认为你应该抓住这个机会
to talk with them.
与他们交谈。
Have a chat. Don't give up.
聊聊吧。不要放弃。
This is something we worked hard to earn.
这是我们努力挣来的。
I'm not very good at this.
我不太擅长这个。
I'm really not good at it.
我真的不擅长。
I'm just... really not good at all.
我只是……真的一点都不好。
Really, I'm not an assertive person.
确实，我不是一个有主见的人。
It's just...
这只是...
And also...
还有...
I feel like crying. This is so frustrating.
我感觉很想哭。这太令人沮丧了。
No, you can't.
不，你不能。
Why do I always cry on this show?
为什么我每次看这个节目都会哭？
So silly.
太傻了。
Then I think you should just pick someone
那我觉得你应该选一个人
you feel good about,
你感觉良好，
and get to know them first.
并首先了解他们。
Follow your heart.
跟随你的心。
I don't want to overthink it either.
我也不想想太多。
This date
这个日期
Rights can also be waived, right?
权利也可以放弃吧？
Invitation selection has ended
邀请评选已结束
I wonder if anyone will ask me out today
不知道今天有没有人约我出去
The island dating zone is now open
岛上约会区现已开放
Please proceed: Fu Jie, Weng Fanqian, Lu Wanfei
Please proceed: Fu Jie, Weng Fanqian, Lu Wanfei
Proceed to the dating area
前往约会区
So hard, help me
太难了，帮帮我吧
Zheng Dedong, please proceed to the dating area
郑德东，请前往交友区
Keep it up
继续努力吧
Your dark circles are so bad, it's hilarious
你的黑眼圈太严重了，太搞笑了
Okay
好的
Zheng Dedong is really popular now
郑德东现在真的很红
Today I chose Zheng Dedong
Today I chose Zheng Dedong
What interests me most today is still Zheng Dedong
今天我最感兴趣的还是郑德东
I like that he has
我喜欢他有
a kind of relaxed vibe
一种轻松的氛围
I have a good relationship with Zheng Dedong
我和郑德东关系很好
I just wanted to interact with Zheng Dedong
我只是想和郑德东互动
Today I definitely only have two
今天我肯定只有两个
You and Zheng Dedong
You and Zheng Dedong
It's a bit unexpected
有点出乎意料
Hello
你好
Are you surprised it's me?
你很惊讶是我吗？
A little surprised
有点惊讶
Today I have the right to choose
今天我有选择的权利
100% means I choose you
100%意味着我选择你
Okay
好的
You look so beautiful today
你今天看起来真漂亮
Really? I'm wearing blue
真的吗？我穿着蓝色
This seat is a bit uncomfortable
这个座位有点不舒服
I want to sit as elegantly as you do
我想像你一样优雅地坐着
Let's change positions
我们换个位置吧
Let's adjust our posture
我们调整一下姿势
Change positions and sit more comfortably
改变姿势，坐得更舒服
Yes, that's better
是的，这样更好
A bit more comfortable now
现在舒服一点了
Stretching out makes a big difference
伸展运动会有很大的不同
Yesterday, they only served greens
昨天，他们只提供蔬菜
But today, we have meat
但今天我们有肉
Are you hungry? Let's eat a little first
你饿了吗？我们先吃一点吧
We can start eating
我们可以开始吃饭了
Let's have a bite first
我们先吃一口
Today is nice
今天天气真好
Thanks to you, we're eating early
多亏了你，我们吃得早了
Let me show you a magic trick
让我给你表演一个魔术
What trick?
什么伎俩？
Here’s a tissue for you
这是给你的纸巾
No wonder you're someone who's been on several dates.
难怪你是一个约会过好几次的人。
I've only been on one date, yesterday.
我昨天只约会过一次。
You mentioned you studied in Australia before.
你提到你以前在澳大利亚留学过。
Australia, Sydney.
澳大利亚，悉尼。
Sydney, Sydney's nice.
悉尼，悉尼真好。
I originally wanted to go to Melbourne.
原本想去墨尔本。
Because back then,
因为那时候，
I was in a relationship during school.
我在学校期间谈过恋爱。
Yeah.
是的。
Then my partner in Sydney went to Melbourne.
然后我在悉尼的伙伴去了墨尔本。
So I thought about going together.
于是就想着一起去。
But in the end,
但最终，
it fell apart—it ended as soon as we went.
它崩溃了——我们一走它就结束了。
Why?
为什么？
Not sure, it's just...
不确定，这只是...
At that time,
当时，
I'm not saying she was bad or I was bad,
我并不是说她不好或者我不好
it's just that back then,
只是那时候
our social circles were different.
我们的社交圈不同。
She lived in Australia,
她住在澳大利亚，
Melbourne life.
墨尔本生活。
I lived in Sydney.
我住在悉尼。
So it was still because of the distance.
所以还是因为距离的原因。
Yeah, the long-distance was the reason.
是的，长途就是原因。
Right after we talked about breaking up,
就在我们谈分手之后，
I still felt like it was nothing.
我还是觉得没什么。
But when I got back to my seat, I suddenly felt—
但当我回到座位上时，我突然觉得——
like my whole mood just sank.
我的整个心情都低落了。
That delayed kind of...
那种延迟的...
Yeah.
是的。
Sudden emotions.
突然的情绪。
Yeah, and then I realized—
是的，然后我意识到——
So this is what it means...
所以这就是它的意思...
That we actually had such deep feelings for each other.
原来我们对彼此的感情如此深厚。
So I actually place great importance on
所以我实际上非常重视
this process of companionship in relationships
这个关系中陪伴的过程
I think it's like
我认为这就像
painting layers on a wall
在墙上画层
As you go through daily life together
当你们一起度过日常生活时
You add one layer, I add another
你加一层，我加另一层
Growing thicker with each layer
每层都变厚
Yes
是的
Then one day
然后有一天
When storms come
当暴风雨来临时
Only after weathering them do you realize
只有经历过它们之后你才会意识到
How thick these layers have become
这些层变得有多厚
Yes
是的
Zheng Dedong is the type who doesn't compete
郑德东是那种不争气的类型
He might chat more about things he likes
他可能会多聊一些他喜欢的事情
But he's not the overly proactive type
但他并不是那种过于主动的类型
This private conversation
这段私人谈话
Made me feel
让我感觉
He's quite comfortable to talk with
和他聊天很舒服
So I wanted to explore more topics
所以我想探索更多的话题
I don't think I've been to Hainan before - this is my first time
我想我以前没去过海南——这是我第一次
How do you say it in Hainanese?
海南话怎么说？
In Hainanese, for example
以海南话为例
If I were from Hainan
假如我是海南人
"You look really nice today"
“你今天看起来真好看”
"You look beautiful today" we would say
我们会说“你今天看起来很漂亮”
We'd say
我们会说
So complicated
好复杂
You look really beautiful today
你今天看起来真漂亮
It emphasizes the word "really"
它强调“真的”这个词
Hainanese has an official version
海南话有正式版了
It's the Wenchang dialect
这是文昌话
Considered the standard version of Hainanese
算是标准版的海南话
Every city and county has different local customs
每个城市、县都有不同的风土人情
Like the food here in Lingshui
喜欢陵水这里的美食
Everything is different
一切都不一样了
If there's a chance, I can take you
如果有机会我可以带你
To visit other cities and counties on the island
游览岛上其他市县
You've made me quite a lot of promises
你给了我很多承诺
Then let me show you a magic trick
那我给你表演一个魔术
There's magic too?
也有魔法？
Do you want to
你想要_____吗
Do you want to see it?
你想看吗？
Want to play?
想玩吗？
Go ahead
前进
Close your eyes
闭上眼睛
Look
看
What's this?
这是什么？
Is this like some sort of answer book?
这像是某种答题书吗？
It's the answer book
这是答题本
Then you choose one first
然后你先选一个
I'll think of a question
我会想一个问题
Then after I open it
然后我打开之后
I'll tell you what my question was, okay?
我来告诉你我的问题是什么，好吗？
Let's go
我们走吧
I've thought of a question, and now I'll
我想到了一个问题，现在我来
Turn
转动
Open it
打开它
Emphasizing participation, that's right
强调参与，没错
Emphasizing participation
强调参与
What's your question?
你有什么问题？
My question is
我的问题是
Would you be willing to keep in touch with me?
你愿意和我保持联系吗？
Actually quite close
其实很接近
Emphasizing participation means
强调参与手段
The meaning is "participation matters most"
意思是“参与最重要”
Participation matters most, right
参与最重要，对吧
This meaning isn't a very good implication
这个意思并不是一个很好的暗示
It also pushes me
也推动着我
Then I should start trying harder
那我应该开始更加努力
I think in reality you might
我认为现实中你可能
Not be too
不太会
The type who's very straightforward
很直接的类型
In reality I might be more
事实上我可能更
Introverted than now
比现在内向
I'm actually quite introverted
其实我很内向
And a rather laid-back person
还有一个比较悠闲的人
I've probably been
我可能已经
Single for about five or six years
单身五六年左右
The reason is also because of my own
原因也是因为我自己
Personality is like this
性格是这样的
My turn
轮到我了
Okay, your turn
好的，轮到你了
Then my question is
那么我的问题是
Will both of us stay tomorrow?
明天我们俩都留下来吗？
Use charm wisely
明智地使用魅力
It's like a hint
这就像一个提示
Like a hint
就像一个提示
That makes some sense
这有一定道理
Yes, that makes some sense
是的，这有一定道理
Then I hope my place in your heart will
那么我希望我在你心中的位置
Be a little more
多一点
When using the Book of Answers
使用答案之书时
She asked
她问
Questions about whether we would survive
关于我们能否生存的问题
Actually still
其实还是
I think she's quite thoughtful
我觉得她考虑得很周到
Her questions all stem from
她的疑问都源于
Considering both of us
考虑到我们俩
So this is what I
所以这就是我
Find most touching about her
找出她最感人的地方
Let me show you another magic trick
让我给你展示另一个魔术
Okay
好的
What's this?
这是什么？
It's a bit like Truth or Dare
有点像真心话大冒险
Let me see first
让我先看看
This question is so boring
这个问题好无聊
When I chose you, did you want to refuse?
当我选择你的时候，你想拒绝吗？
Why?
为什么？
How could I refuse?
我怎么能拒绝呢？
Right
正确的
This one's boring, let's take it out
这个很无聊，我们把它去掉吧
A bit boring
有点无聊
Who would refuse Weng Fanxi?
Who would refuse Weng Fanxi?
Let me draw one
让我画一张
If you had to list
如果你必须列出
Your top three ideal dates
您最理想的三个约会
Who would they be?
他们会是谁？
So
所以
My first choice
我的第一选择
Is you
是你吗
It's you
是你
And the second is
第二个是
Xiao Enya
Xiao Enya
Can you do me a favor?
你能帮我一个忙吗？
Go ahead.
前进。
Can you help me put this on?
你能帮我穿上这个吗？
Sure, which side?
当然可以，哪一边？
This side.
这一边。
Okay.
好的。
Alright, I'm coming over.
好的，我这就过来。
Just think about it, clip it on like this.
想一想，像这样夹起来。
Or maybe pin it on the side like this?
或者像这样把它钉在一边？
That works, you're so clever.
原来如此，你太聪明了
Is this okay?
这样可以吗？
Done.
完毕。
Does this look good?
这看起来不错吗？
Looks good.
看起来不错。
Good.
好的。
Of course.
当然。
Then it's settled.
然后就解决了。
The whole set will be complete.
整套就完成了。
This will add a nice touch.
这会增加一个很好的触感。
Yes, all done.
是的，一切都完成了。
So that means...
所以这意味着...
Today's magic show...
今天的魔术表演...
ends here.
到此结束。
Can you hold my bag for me?
你能帮我拿一下我的包吗？
Sure.
当然。
Alright.
好吧。
Take it slow.
慢慢来。
I'm really quite happy today.
我今天真的很开心。
Do you know why?
你知道为什么吗？
Why?
为什么？
It's because I was feeling a bit passive yesterday.
因为昨天我感觉有点被动。
I was just really anxious.
我只是真的很着急。
But today,
但今天，
I started to feel
我开始感觉到
that this game is actually fun.
这个游戏其实很有趣。
You should go this way.
你应该走这条路。
Okay, I'll go this way.
好吧，我就往这边走。
This makes you look taller.
这会让你看起来更高。
Is it
是吗
This is a bit more harmonious
这样比较和谐一点
Thank you
谢谢
Thank you. You're welcome
谢谢。不客气
An extremely tough path
一条极其艰难的道路
The person I finally invited for a date was Chen Mengjia
我最终邀请约会的人是陈梦佳
Because yesterday, I noticed
因为昨天我注意到
Mengjia was actually dressed very beautifully
孟佳其实穿得很漂亮
But she seemed a bit down
但她似乎有点情绪低落
So I thought
所以我想
If I had this chance
如果我有这个机会
I wanted to give her
我想给她
This kind of island date experience
这样的海岛约会体验
Hello
你好
Nice to meet you
很高兴见到你
I'm your blind date
我是你的相亲对象
I'm glad you came to meet me
我很高兴你能来见我
I'm happy too
我也很高兴
Before sunset
日落之前
We didn't schedule fireworks
我们没有安排烟花表演
So I hope this can be
所以我希望这可以是
the kind of date you'd enjoy
你喜欢的约会类型
That sounds nice
听起来不错
Actually I was thinking
其实我在想
We could both wear comfortable clothes
我们都可以穿舒适的衣服
Have some casual food and beer
吃点休闲食品和啤酒
Here, let's eat
来，我们吃饭吧
Okay
好的
Then let's have a relaxed date
那么我们来一次轻松的约会吧
When you sat here, I could tell
当你坐在这里时，我可以告诉
This is very relaxed
这是非常放松的
You smiled when you saw me
当你看到我时你微笑了
Cute
可爱的
What you're wearing today
你今天穿什么
Is it the same as yesterday?
和昨天一样吗？
No it's different
不，这是不同的
See?
看？
Little details
小细节
Very nice, very pretty
非常好，非常漂亮
Yesterday was a tube top with pants
昨天是抹胸配裤子
You typical straight guy
你这个典型的直男
Okay
好的
Well
出色地
When you heard
当你听到
me call your name
我叫你的名字
No, when the announcement called your name
不，当公告喊到你的名字时
What did you think? How did you feel?
你觉得怎么样？你感觉如何？
I thought
我以为
Is he apologizing for not choosing me today?
他是在为今天没有选择我而道歉吗？
Is that why he came?
这就是他来的原因？
Okay
好的
So why did you want to date me?
那你为什么想和我约会？
Didn't I agree to it?
我不是同意了吗？
Between the two of us here, who would you rather date?
我们两个人，你更愿意和谁约会？
Her
她
I've talked with her the most
我和她聊得最多的
Because you promised me
因为你答应过我
Right
正确的
Okay
好的
Alright, no problem
好的，没问题
I said if I ever get to go on a date
我说如果我有机会去约会的话
I'd choose you
我会选择你
Great
伟大的
And yesterday
还有昨天
You looked really beautiful
你看起来真的很漂亮
But
但
You wanted to date but couldn't get a date
你想约会但没能找到约会对象
I obviously know that
我显然知道
Thank you
谢谢
For making my first date on this island
为了在这个岛上进行我的第一次约会
I'm happy it's with me
我很高兴它和我在一起
I'm happy too
我也很高兴
Because
因为
You're my
你是我的
Main guest
主要嘉宾
But I have to admit
但我不得不承认
I think when we two normally
我想当我们两个平时
chat casually, I feel quite comfortable
闲聊，感觉挺舒服的
The reason you're uncomfortable today is
你今天不舒服的原因是
I don't know
我不知道
I know
我知道
Because my back is exposed
因为我的背暴露了
You're nervous
你很紧张
Sweating all over thinking
想想都出汗
Her back is so smooth
她的背是如此光滑
Anyway I think maybe
无论如何我想也许
You're a little nervous
你有点紧张
I think
我认为
Walking after dinner, you might be more nervous
饭后散步，你可能会更紧张
Because someone might twist their ankle here
因为有人可能会在这里扭伤脚踝
And fall down
并跌倒
When I'm with her I can joke around
当我和她在一起时我可以开玩笑
It's extremely relaxed and pleasant
非常轻松愉快
We just talk very happily
我们只是聊得很开心
But actually
但实际上
Over all these days
这些天来
Our communication
我们的沟通
Probably counts as the most
大概算最多的
Yes, you're the guy I've talked with most
是的，你是我聊得最多的人
You too
你也是
Right
正确的
Do you think you're brave
你认为你很勇敢吗
when it comes to love?
当谈到爱情时？
Not brave.
不勇敢。
If I really like someone,
如果我真的喜欢一个人
I'd rather miss the chance than take the initiative.
我宁愿错过机会，也不愿主动出击。
No, I think strong feelings
不，我认为有强烈的感情
definitely take time to develop.
肯定需要时间来发展。
Rushing into decisions
仓促做出决定
or anything like that...
或者类似的东西...
seems a bit immature to me.
对我来说似乎有点不成熟。
I understand what you mean.
我明白你的意思。
Right, that's exactly why
没错，正是因为如此
I try to avoid doing that.
我尽量避免这样做。
Yes, I think the most enjoyable
是的，我认为最愉快的
relationship between two people is
两个人之间的关系是
first getting to know each other,
初次相识，
then after that,
然后在那之后，
if there's mutual interest, take it further.
如果有共同利益，就进一步发展。
If not,
如果不，
staying friends is just fine, right?
保持朋友关系就好了，对吧？
That's exactly how I feel too.
我也有这样的感觉。
The reason I didn't choose you was because
我没有选择你的原因是因为
I had no idea
我不知道
that those I didn't choose might have to leave the island
那些我没有选择的人可能不得不离开这个岛
Actually, my thinking was very simple
其实我的想法很简单
I just felt
我只是觉得
I'd promised you before
我之前就答应过你
And yesterday when I saw you
昨天当我看到你的时候
unhappy, I truly
不开心，我真的
felt quite sad in my heart, so
我心里感到很悲伤，所以
felt sad
感到悲伤
Yes, I just thought
是的，我只是想
If I got the chance, and I happened to win today
如果我有机会的话，今天我碰巧赢了
I would bring you along
我会带你一起去
Even if you blame me
就算你责怪我
or feel disappointed in me
或者对我感到失望
I actually
我其实
don't care about these things
不关心这些事情
I'm not saying I don't care about your feelings
我并不是说我不关心你的感受
but rather I believe
但我相信
I just need to do what I can
我只需要做我能做的
If
如果
it's hard to predict, you know
很难预测，你知道
it's just hard to predict
很难预测
Actually, that feeling
其实那种感觉
wasn't like lovers' feelings
不像恋人的感觉
but rather
而是
because you're
因为你是
the only person I'm closest to here
我在这里唯一最亲近的人
and I felt
我觉得
I think maybe he doesn't want to see me anymore
我想也许他不想再见到我了
So
所以
I'm not
我不是
I know, that was just my thinking at the time
我知道，这只是我当时的想法
And I was also afraid you'd feel burdened
我也担心你会感到有负担
So I also hope you won't feel guilty
所以我也希望你不要感到内疚
Actually
实际上
Do you know when I
你知道我什么时候
started feeling guilty?
开始感到内疚？
When?
什么时候？
It was when I heard them
就在我听到他们的时候
start talking about how
开始谈论如何
those who weren't chosen
那些没有被选中的人
would have to leave the island
必须离开该岛
That's when I began to realize
那时我开始意识到
how things really were
事情到底是怎样的
I voted for you every day because
我每天都投票给你，因为
even if I had to leave
即使我不得不离开
I wanted you to always stay here
我希望你永远留在这里
I think
我认为
I hope during this journey
我希望在这段旅程中
you can just relax
你可以放松一下
Even if they're not your teammates today
即使他们今天不是你的队友
If your heart tells you
如果你的心告诉你
"I want to choose them"
“我想选择他们”
I completely understand and respect that
我完全理解并尊重这一点
The essence of this game
这个游戏的精髓
is to follow your heart
就是跟随你的心
and like who you want to like
并喜欢你​​想喜欢的人
I'm glad you could tell me this
我很高兴你能告诉我这个
I've reconsidered
我重新考虑过
whether what we have is friendship or love
无论我们拥有的是友情还是爱情
I found it's more friendship, so
我发现这更多的是友谊，所以
I can face my feelings more directly
我可以更直接地面对自己的感受
But when we're together
但当我们在一起的时候
whether walking or talking
无论是走路还是说话
I feel quite happy
我觉得很幸福
I think being happy is enough
我觉得开心就足够了
Okay, fine, we've made up
好吧，好吧，我们和好了
Alright, we're good now
好吧，我们现在很好
Before we...
在我们...
Previously we...
此前我们...
Had we already... you know?
我们已经……你知道吗？
Had we fallen out?
我们闹翻了吗？
In my heart I felt
我心里感到
What?
什么？
Just this kind of...
就这样的...
You know how in the later stages...
你知道后期如何...
But do you know what girls like?
但你知道女孩子喜欢什么吗？
If next time you meet
如果下次见面
a girl you like
你喜欢的女孩
Most girls actually want to feel special
大多数女孩实际上想要感觉特别
Then you should be braver
那你就应该勇敢一点
Show her all your love
向她展示你全部的爱
Not just talk about plans or whatever
不只是谈论计划或其他什么
I didn't mention plans
我没有提到计划
I never talked about plans
我从未谈论过计划
I don't know who's nitpicking me
我不知道谁在挑剔我
Fine
美好的
Alright then
那么好吧
Whatever
任何
I don't even want to be elegant anymore
我什至不想再优雅了
How much longer?
还要多久？
This is so annoying
这太烦人了
When will this end? I can't take it
这一切什么时候才能结束？我受不了
Throw it on the ground
把它扔在地上
Be careful
当心
Help
帮助
The situation I imagined has happened
我想象的情况发生了
It's fine
没关系
My elegance
我的优雅
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
I'm fine
我很好
Not elegant at all
一点也不优雅
This is a slope.
这是一个斜坡。
Should we still change this?
我们还应该改变这一点吗？
The male guest dining with you.
与您一起用餐的男客人。
Let's walk over to the restaurant.
我们去餐厅走走吧。
Then see what they're eating.
然后看看他们吃什么。
Fu Jie.
Fu Jie.
Fireworks are going off across the way.
对面正在放烟花。
So beautiful it's "to die for."
如此美丽，令人“为之而死”。
They're quite grand.
他们相当伟大。
Isn't this making up for it?
这不是弥补吗？
You mentioned my wish list.
你提到了我的愿望清单。
Yes.
是的。
Quite romantic.
相当浪漫。
Yesterday, a few of us.
昨天，我们几个人。
who didn't get a chance to go on a date.
谁没有机会去约会。
were sitting together.
坐在一起。
when we heard fireworks across the way.
当我们听到对面有烟花的声音时。
She told me.
她告诉我。
she was looking forward to a date with fireworks too.
她也期待着一场烟花约会。
I'm so glad today.
今天我很高兴。
when I took her on a date.
当我带她去约会时。
fireworks went off across the way.
烟花在路对面燃放。
It fulfilled this little wish of hers.
也算是满足了她这个小小的心愿。
Fireworks again
又放烟花了
What's the occasion these days?
这几天是什么场合？
I don't know how to choose
我不知道如何选择
I should just give up
我应该放弃
Hello
你好
This date
这个日期
Rights can be given up too, right?
权利也可以放弃吧？
You can't give up
你不能放弃
I feel like we finally won for once
我感觉我们终于赢了一次
so we shouldn't lose the initiative in this date
所以我们不应该在这个日期失去主动权
[implied in previous line]
[前一行暗示]
Jiang Shangru chose me on the first day with that
江尚儒第一天就选择了我就是这样
love declaration
爱情宣言
But after all, it was them
但毕竟是他们
who spent these past few days together first
这几天是谁先在一起度过的
I don't want to
我不想
interfere with others' getting-to-know-each-other process
干扰他人相互了解的过程
I'm just afraid that if I choose Jiang Shangru
我只是害怕如果我选择姜尚如
then she (Hu Wei) might get upset
那么她（胡伟）可能会不高兴
So I hope to get her consent first
所以我希望先得到她的同意
Hu Wei
Hu Wei
Come here
来这里
Well...
出色地...
It's just that...
只是那...
Although we won the competition today
虽然我们今天赢得了比赛
Right
正确的
So she wanted to ask if she could choose Jiang Shangru
所以她想问问她是否可以选择姜尚儒
But she's really afraid
但她真的很害怕
worried it might hurt your relationship
担心这会伤害你们的关系
Sure, no problem.
当然，没问题。
Then I think...
那么我想...
Okay, no issue.
好的，没问题。
Crying over this matter...
为这件事哭了...
Right.
正确的。
I think you're really good to me.
我觉得你对我真的很好。
It's fine.
没关系。
Just talking it out helps.
只要说出来就有帮助。
No worries.
不用担心。
I'm going to shower.
我要去洗澡了。
Okay.
好的。
Go shower quickly.
赶紧去洗澡吧。
It's just that everyone is...
只是大家都...
...in the process of getting to know each other.
……在互相了解的过程中。
So...
所以...
I respect every choice people make...
我尊重人们的每一个选择...
...and respect them.
...并尊重他们。
I believe there are...
我相信有...
...their own reasons and stories.
...他们自己的理由和故事。
Hello.
你好。
Are we having steak?
我们吃牛排吗？
Yes.
是的。
I hope you win today.
我希望你今天赢了。
How so?
为何如此？
Then I won't have to choose.
那我就不用选了
Is that so?
是这样吗？
I'm so nervous right now.
我现在很紧张。
Me too.
我也是。
It's just...
这只是...
Just what?
只是什么？
It's just my first date, suddenly...
这只是我第一次约会，突然...
If this is...
如果这是...
Is this your first date?
这是你第一次约会吗？
I've never dated before.
我以前从未约会过。
Yes, my first date.
是的，我的第一次约会。
So I'm a bit nervous.
所以我有点紧张。
Don't worry, I got you something.
别担心，我给你带了东西。
What did you get?
你得到了什么？
Today's prize.
今天的奖品。
I got you an eye mask.
我给你买了眼罩。
Because the light...
因为光...
Eye mask?
眼罩？
Yes, the light might not turn off.
是的，灯可能不会关闭。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Appreciate it.
欣赏它。
Okay, eat up.
好吧，吃饱吧。
Go ahead and eat.
继续吃饭吧。
You have some.
你有一些。
If you don't mind.
如果你不介意的话。
No, you have more.
不，你还有更多。
I think you should eat more.
我觉得你应该多吃一点。
Because I heard...
因为我听到...
They said they only had salad yesterday.
他们说昨天只吃了沙拉。
Right.
正确的。
Yes.
是的。
But the salad had meat and shrimp in it.
但沙拉里有肉和虾。
You had a date yesterday.
你昨天有个约会。
So you've had two dates now.
所以你们现在已经有过两次约会了。
Yesterday you were chosen, today you're choosing.
昨天你被选择了，今天你正在选择。
So difficult.
太难了。
Why would you say that?
你为什么这么说？
Because I think you all...
因为我想你们都...
Because you've been with Hu Wei these past few days
因为这几天你一直和胡伟在一起
You two got along
你们两个相处得很融洽
Hu Wei is really nice, and he's been kind to me too
胡伟真的很好，他对我也很好
So I just...
所以我只是...
Actually, I think the reason we all came here is
事实上，我认为我们来到这里的原因是
we definitely still want to
我们绝对还想
maintain good relationships with everyone
与每个人都保持良好的关系
Because my main purpose in coming here
因为我来这里的主要目的
was to hopefully get along with everyone
是希望能和大家和睦相处
and interact well
并互动良好
to become good friends with everyone
和大家成为好朋友
and create wonderful memories
并创造美好的回忆
on this island together
一起在这个岛上
That's good then
那就好
Yes, so when you said you wanted to chat with me
是的，所以当你说你想和我聊天时
I was actually really happy about it
我真的很高兴
The common understanding we all share is
我们大家的共同认识是
we should get to know each other more.
我们应该更多地了解彼此。
Meeting in this place
在这个地方见面
wasn't easy to begin with.
开始并不容易。
So I really hope that
所以我真的希望
I can leave a good impression on everyone.
我能给大家留下一个好印象。
I feel that today
我感觉今天
I've actually been serious
其实我是认真的
After some reflection these past three days,
经过这三天的反思，
I might have been too passive.
可能是我太被动了。
I genuinely don't know how to interact with guys.
我真的不知道如何与男生相处。
I want to talk with you more because
我想和你多聊聊因为
I've been watching you often.
我经常观察你。
During the first game we played,
在我们玩的第一场比赛中，
I wanted to team up with you but then changed my mind.
我本来想和你组队，但后来改变了主意。
And you chose me in your love declaration too.
而你在爱情宣言中也选择了我。
Right.
正确的。
I was just about to mention that.
我正要提到这一点。
At that time,
当时，
when I said I chose you in my love declaration,
当我说我在爱情宣言中选择了你时，
you gave me a certain look
你给了我一个特定的眼神
that made me wonder if you were upset with me or...
这让我想知道你是否生我的气或者...
The photo I chose was of a girl in a dress,
我选择的照片是一个穿着裙子的女孩，
and it should have been...
它本来应该是...
Yes.
是的。
No, I'm just surprised.
不，我只是很惊讶。
Because...
因为...
I... I would also wonder about this.
我……我也想知道这个问题。
I wanted to say...
我想说...
What exactly did I say
我到底说了什么
that would make a girl feel awkward?
这会让女孩感到尴尬吗？
I think I would reflect on this too.
我想我也会反思这一点。
It's not awkwardness, it's shyness.
这不是尴尬，而是害羞。
Shyness, I can understand that.
害羞，我能理解。
Then on the first day...
然后第一天...
Even though we didn't interact much that first day,
虽然第一天我们没有太多互动
but I still gave you...
但我还是给了你...
On the first day I voted for Jiang Shangru.
第一天我就把票投给了姜尚儒。
During group activities,
在集体活动中，
his behavior
他的行为
was something I really admired.
这是我真正钦佩的事情。
That type of guy...
那种人...
Very gentlemanly.
很有绅士风度。
I wanted to get to know him better.
我想更好地了解他。
I'm really passive.
我实在是太被动了。
If a guy doesn't approach me first,
如果一个男人不先接近我
then I might just...
那我可能就...
I'd rather miss the chance
我宁愿错过机会
than make the first move.
而不是迈出第一步。
I think girls...
我认为女孩...
Girls like this are really "annoying," you know?
这样的女孩子真的很“烦人”你知道吗？
With me being like this, do you also...
我都这样了，你是不是也...
feel like you can't fully relax and be yourself?
感觉自己无法完全放松并做自己？
I'm pretty relaxed now.
我现在很放松。
That's good then.
那就好了。
No, I think...
不，我想...
I think you really have to talk
我觉得你真的需要谈谈
to know what someone's like.
了解某人的性格。
Because I feel...
因为我觉得...
after hearing you say all this,
听你说了这一切之后
I'm seeing different sides of you.
我看到了你不同的一面。
People really need to spend time together to understand each other.
人们确实需要花时间在一起才能互相理解。
Would you like to eat some more?
你还想再吃一点吗？
I haven't touched this, you should eat it.
我没碰过这个，你应该吃它。
Go ahead and eat.
继续吃饭吧。
Don't look at me like that.
别这样看着我。
Is there anything on my mouth?
我嘴里有东西吗？
What's wrong with your mouth?
你的嘴怎么了？
Did something get on it?
是不是有东西沾到上面了？
No.
不。
You look especially beautiful when you smile.
你微笑的时候看起来特别美丽。
Your smile is really lovely.
你的笑容真的很可爱。
Really?
真的吗？
Truly.
确实。
Is that so?
是这样吗？
How so?
为何如此？
And I feel like your teeth seem to sparkle.
我觉得你的牙齿似乎闪闪发光。
It's like...
这就像...
What is it?
它是什么？
Special.
特别的。
What's that idiom... it's...
这是什么成语啊……
Bright eyes and white teeth.
明亮的眼睛和洁白的牙齿。
Sparkling eyes and pearly whites.
闪闪发光的眼睛和珍珠白。
Your eyes shine too, and...
你的眼睛也闪闪发亮，而且……
Your teeth gleam as well.
你的牙齿也闪闪发光。
You're so good with words.
你的言辞真好。
Too much.
太多了。
I shouldn't praise you.
我不应该夸你。
Don't.
不。
You're making my "tail" wag.
你让我的“尾巴”摇起来。
No, not at all.
不，一点也不。
It's okay.
没关系。
I'm really happy with this decision now.
我现在对这个决定真的很满意。
My initial impression of you and...
我对你的最初印象...
what I guessed you might do...
我猜你可能会做什么...
to now having meals like this...
到现在吃这样的饭菜...
and talking about these things, I think you're great.
谈论这些事情，我认为你很棒。
Really great.
真的很棒。
Actually, I'm quite happy.
其实我挺高兴的。
After the date with him, I feel quite relaxed.
和他约会后，我感觉很轻松。
Yes, it's like...
是的，这就像...
being with a friend.
和朋友在一起。
Before establishing a relationship...
在建立关系之前...
I think it's good to meet more people.
我觉得认识更多的人是件好事。
Only then can you know...
只有这样你才能知道...
what you truly want.
你真正想要的是什么。
Let me ask you something...
让我问你一件事...
If you were to win today...
如果你今天赢了...
who would you choose?
你会选择谁？
I would choose Hu Wei.
我会选择胡伟。
Fireworks again
又放烟花了
What's the occasion these days?
这几天是什么场合？
Come quick, look at the fireworks!
快来吧，看烟花！
Exactly the same as yesterday, right?
和昨天一模一样吧？
Pretty much
差不多
So beautiful
如此美丽
I wonder if I can chew this.
我想知道我是否可以咀嚼这个。
This one's better.
这个更好。
Here you go.
干得好。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Here.
这里。
Wipe it for her.
给她擦一下。
Turn around.
回转。
Today I
今天我
even lost all my makeup
甚至把我的妆都卸掉了
By the way
顺便一提
I’ve always thought you two look alike
我一直觉得你们两个很像
Do we really look alike?
我们真的很像吗？
Alright, peace
好吧，平安
I also think you two look very similar
我也觉得你们两个看起来很相似
How do I look like him?
我怎么看起来像他？
No, they share that kind of resemblance
不，他们有那种相似之处
A couple’s resemblance, not just looking alike
情侣之间的相似，不仅仅是长相相似
I’ll bring my machine gun
我会带上我的机枪
I’ll bring mine too
我也带上我的
What’s your problem?
你有什么问题吗？
I'll go first
我先去
I'm done eating, I'll head out first
吃饱了，我先出去了
Sit
坐
Goodbye
再见
You actually said goodbye
你其实已经说了再见
No
不
You really said goodbye, I can't believe
你真的说再见了，我不敢相信
Quite high emotional intelligence
情商相当高
You're not much better
你也好不了多少
Just drop it
只要放下它
Received
已收到
Your sister is really adorable
你妹妹真的很可爱
Your brother is cute too
你弟弟也很可爱
You're equally matched "jokers"
你们是同样匹配的“小丑”
Equally matched?
不相上下？
Perfectly matched
完美搭配
I'm back
我回来了
Let's go
我们走吧
Okay
好的
Goodbye
再见
I'm leaving now, goodbye
我现在要走了，再见
Thank you for choosing me today
谢谢你今天选择了我
Okay, goodbye
好的，再见
How was it?
它怎么样？
I was quite happy
我很高兴
I didn't expect you to react this way
我没想到你会有这样的反应
You only get to know someone by spending time together
你只有通过花时间在一起才能了解一个人
Right
正确的
You have to spend time together to know
你必须花时间在一起才能知道
He's here
他在这里
How was the date?
约会怎么样？
I got to know her a bit
我对她有了一点了解
Was it okay?
还好吗？
It was completely different from what I imagined
和我想象的完全不一样
I think she's really nice
我觉得她真的很好
During the date, she helped me
约会期间，她帮助了我
understand and know her better
更好地理解和了解她
I think she's really great
我觉得她真的很棒
She's very brave
她很勇敢
Zheng Dedong seems a bit...
Zheng Dedong seems a bit...
Not entirely honest, that's the impression I get.
不完全诚实，这就是我的印象。
It seems like he's not...
看来他不是...
very invested in this matter.
对这件事非常投入。
Right.
正确的。
Isn't that right? Isn't it?
是不是这样？不是吗？
I never expected my former partner...
没想到我以前的搭档...
Zheng Dedong would choose me.
Zheng Dedong would choose me.
Xiao Enya, come on.
肖恩雅，加油。
He didn't give me any signals today.
今天他没有给我任何信号。
I want to know how he truly feels.
我想知道他的真实感受。
I hope his feelings match mine.
我希望他的感受和我的一样。
Or that he'd just tell me directly.
或者他会直接告诉我。
I don't want this to be ambiguous.
我不想让这件事含糊不清。
You chose me today - you owe me an explanation.
你今天选择了我——你欠我一个解释。
Do you like me or not?
你喜欢我还是不喜欢我？
If not, forget it.
如果没有，就忘记它吧。
Don't be like this.
别这样。
So aggressive when you speak.
说话的时候那么咄咄逼人。
Learn from me.
向我学习。
Okay.
好的。
Why did you choose me today?
为什么你今天选择了我？
This is how I talk.
我就是这样说话的。
This is my way of speaking.
这是我的说话方式。
Then I'll say it like this.
那我就这样说吧。
I'll just ask him: Why did you choose me today?
我就问他：你今天为什么选择我？
You should say it like this.
你应该这样说。
Actually, when you chose me today...
事实上，当你今天选择了我...
I was both surprised and quite happy.
我既惊讶又非常高兴。
I've expressed my feelings to you before...
我已经向你表达过我的感受了...
but you didn't seem very responsive.
但你看起来反应不太积极。
I didn't expect you to choose me today.
没想到你今天竟然选择了我。
Your choice made me very happy.
你的选择让我很开心。
I feel like I got a response.
我感觉我得到了回应。
So am I wrong about this?
那么我在这件事上有错吗？
Would I be?
我会吗？
More or less.
或多或少。
Let's talk.
我们来谈谈吧。
Okay, have a seat.
好的，请坐。
I really needed to talk to you today.
我今天真的需要和你谈谈。
Because I...
因为我...
You were certain about talking to me?
你确定要跟我说话吗？
Yes.
是的。
You know how I am...
你知道我是怎样的人...
My worst trait is being too passive.
我最大的缺点就是太被动。
Why did you choose me today?
为什么你今天选择了我？
First, I don't like ambiguity.
首先，我不喜欢模棱两可。
Let me be straightforward with you...
让我直接跟你说吧...
I definitely have feelings for you.
我绝对对你有感觉。
I understand now.
我现在明白了。
Yes, I'm someone who's very open.
是的，我是一个非常开放的人。
And let me tell you directly...
让我直接告诉你...
Do you have...
你有...
feelings for me? So...
对我的感情？所以...
Or is it
或者是
really just because
真的只是因为
I absolutely don’t want you to leave the island
我绝对不想让你离开这个岛
and then chose you
然后选择了你
I have
我有
70% is not wanting you to leave the island
70% 不希望你离开这个岛
30% is because of how we get along
30%是因为我们相处的方式
and then I’ve developed some feelings for you
然后我对你产生了一些感情
I'm surprised
我很惊讶
My first instinct was that I must keep all of us
我的第一直觉是我必须保留我们所有人
who were originally in the same tent together
原本一起在同一个帐篷里的人
I knew Xiao Enya would probably choose Guo Xu
我就知道肖恩雅很可能会选择郭旭
Guo Xu honestly told me
郭旭老实告诉我
that he has some feelings for Xiao Enya
说明他对肖恩雅有一些感情
So I thought
所以我想
if I could, I should try to help him
如果可以的话，我应该尽力帮助他
to build a bridge for their communication
为他们搭建沟通的桥梁
if they're both willing to cross it
如果他们都愿意跨越它
Attention all islanders
所有岛民请注意
The Scale of Preference is now open
偏好等级现已开放
Time to cast your heart's weights
是时候释放你内心的重量了
Please deliver your heartfelt choices
请说出你的真心选择
Friendly reminder: someone may not leave tomorrow
友情提醒：明天可能有人不会离开
Not tomorrow
不是明天
Only three weights available today
目前仅提供三种重量
Making each heartfelt choice more valuable
让每一次真心的选择更有价值
This is quite unexpected
这是非常出乎意料的
Why did it change to three?
为什么变成了三呢？
I originally planned to split evenly
本来是打算平摊的
With three, there will definitely be
有了三个，肯定会有
issues of having one more or one less
多一或少一的问题
Please face your true feelings more honestly
请更诚实地面对自己的真实感受
Things are getting interesting
事情变得有趣了
Who will your scale favor today?
今天你的体重秤会偏爱谁？
I'm really not the proactive type
我确实不是主动型的人
I don't know why either
我也不知道为什么
If you don't take initiative, there's no chance
如果你不主动，就没有机会
All in on one
全部合一
I've made up my mind
我已经下定决心
Going all in
全力以赴
No need to try so hard to take initiative
不需要那么努力去主动
I think there needs to be some attraction
我认为需要有一些吸引力
Are you feeling conflicted now?
你现在感觉很矛盾吗？
My heart is still there
我的心还在
But I think she's very serious
但我觉得她很认真
I don't know how to choose
我不知道如何选择
But I feel that
但我觉得
making the girl feel comfortable
让女孩感觉舒服
means I still haven't decided, right?
意思是我还没有决定，对吧？
No decision
没有决定
Does this make me a jerk for doing this?
这会让我成为一个混蛋吗？
I reflect on myself like this every day
我每天都这样反省自己
Just think about me
想想我吧
Your smile is particularly beautiful
你的笑容特别美丽
Really?
真的吗？
With bright eyes and gleaming teeth
拥有明亮的眼睛和闪亮的牙齿
I'm very happy with this decision now
我现在对这个决定非常满意
Today I'm 100% sure I'll choose you
今天我百分百确定我会选择你
You look so beautiful today
你今天看起来真漂亮
Really?
真的吗？
Yes, you look very beautiful today
是的，你今天看起来很漂亮
Thank you, Enya
谢谢你，恩雅
You chose me when selecting a male partner
你在选择男伴时选择了我
Our communication has improved significantly
我们的沟通有了显着改善
Can't completely block the sunlight for you
无法为你完全遮挡阳光
It's very comfortable and relaxed
非常舒适放松
I can clearly tell you're talking more than before
我可以清楚地看出你比以前说得更多
You two are equally matched "comedy duo"
你们两个是旗鼓相当的“喜剧二人组”
This is a tough choice
这是一个艰难的选择
This time, there are three weights of affection
这一次，三重情意
So I'll still follow my heart
所以我还是会跟随自己的心
Enya, come on
恩雅，加油
There's a 30% chance I might develop feelings for you
我有 30% 的机会对你产生感情
The sunlight can't shield you completely
阳光无法完全遮蔽你
If anyone takes that step forward
如果有人向前迈出了这一步
I might lean toward them
我可能会倾向于他们
It depends on your actions—still so...
这取决于你的行动——仍然如此......
If you're not proactive, then there's nothing I can do
如果你不主动的话我也无能为力
You've really put in some effort
你确实付出了一些努力
Between Mengjia and me, I feel
我和孟佳之间，我感觉
our bond is truly unbreakable.
我们的纽带确实牢不可破。
We had amazing teamwork today.
今天我们的团队合作非常出色。
Tonight
今晚
I gave two votes to Daniel
我给丹尼尔投了两票
If it weren't for Daniel
如果不是丹尼尔
I wouldn't be on the show today
我今天不会出现在节目中
And I'm grateful he saved my life today
我很感激他今天救了我的命
And one vote went to my first choice Gu Zhenxiang
还有一票投给了我的第一选择顾振祥
I still think he's
我仍然认为他是
a good person and also handsome
人很好，也很帅
He meets my aesthetic standards
他符合我的审美标准
Could you ask
你能问一下吗
Gu Zhenxiang to come see me later?
Gu Zhenxiang to come see me later?
Okay
好的
Who did you say?
你说谁？
Gu Zhenxiang
Gu Zhenxiang
Gu Zhenxiang is my next
Gu Zhenxiang is my next
dating goal that I'll strive for
我会努力实现的约会目标
So conflicted
好矛盾
Right, I just remembered something
对了，我刚刚想起一件事
Chen Mengjia asked you to find her after this
陈梦佳让你在这之后去找她
A bit later
稍后
Now you've made me conflicted
现在你让我很矛盾
You shouldn't have told me
你不应该告诉我
You should've told me after voting
你应该在投票后告诉我
Great, now he's feeling the same way I am
太好了，现在他的感觉和我一样了
You're so mean
你太刻薄了
You shouldn't have told me at all
你根本不应该告诉我
I should've waited until after voting to say anything
我应该等到投票后才说什么
Are you conflicted?
你很矛盾吗？
Then I probably don't feel as conflicted as you.
那我可能就不会像你一样感到矛盾了。
I'm seriously torn.
我严重撕裂了。
Today it's three
今天三点了
There are only three weights.
只有三个权重。
We can't split it equally anymore
我们不能再平分了
A choice must be made
必须做出选择
I had originally made up my mind
我原本就已经下定决心
to give all my votes to Hu Wei
把我的票全部投给胡伟
But when it came time to actually vote
但当真正投票的时候
I started thinking
我开始思考
that Lu Wanfei has really been trying hard
陆婉菲真的很努力
Because I understand how tough it is
因为我明白这有多艰难
to summon that kind of courage
鼓起那种勇气
She mustered the courage to do
她鼓起勇气去做
what she normally
她通常做什么
wouldn’t do in daily life
日常生活中不会做
So I’m considering giving her one of my votes
所以我正在考虑给她一票
Always forcing myself to take the initiative
总是强迫自己采取主动
It's exhausting
真累
So conflicted
好矛盾
Headache
头痛
You're making me conflicted
你让我很矛盾
Okay, I won't wash my hands today
好吧，我今天不洗手
Turn around
回转
Any changes today?
今天有什么变化吗？
Guess.
猜测。
Be nicer to me.
对我好一点。
Why are you being mean to me?
你为什么对我这么刻薄？
I heard the food at today's date was delicious.
听说今天的饭菜很好吃。
Better than mine.
比我的好。
Yes.
是的。
Honestly, more tiring than my work.
说实话，比我的工作还累。
Gu Zhenxiang is my next
Gu Zhenxiang is my next
goal for a date.
约会的目标。
I'm actually really happy chatting with you.
其实我真的很高兴和你聊天。